{
    "subject": "resource/Bal\u00e1zs_Szokolay",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Living_people",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay is Living people.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8294772505760193,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.812859058380127,
            "question": "How has Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay contributed to society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.793941855430603,
            "question": "Is Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay still alive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7366858720779419,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7001683712005615,
            "question": "Where is Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6872497797012329,
            "question": "What is Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6696974635124207,
            "question": "What does Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.577815055847168,
            "question": "What is Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay's legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.525662899017334,
            "question": "Is there anything unique about Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay's work or profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4427807629108429,
            "question": "Has Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay achieved any notable accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay is Living people.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1249_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything unique about Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay's work or profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1249_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay's legacy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1249_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1249_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1249_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I will evaluate whether the information supports the triple \"The subject of Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay is Living people\".\n\nHere's my evaluation:\n\n* From the documents, it can be seen that Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay was born in 1961 and has been alive since then. This suggests that he is indeed a living person.\n* There is no information provided that contradicts this fact.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Bal\u00e1zs Szokolay, including his date of birth (1961), current roles such as professor at the Franz Liszt Academy of Music and guestprofessor at the University of Graz, which indicates that he is a living person."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}